University of Connecticut, Thomas J. Dodd Research Center Records 1998.0290
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
University of Connecticut, Thomas J. Dodd Research Center Records
undated, 1965-
1998.0290
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
38.45 Linear feet
Archives & Special Collections, located at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, was created by the merger of Special Collections and Historical Manuscripts and Archives in 1995. The new area moved into the Dodd Center upon its opening. President William Clinton officiated at the dedication of the Center and kicked off the "Dodd Year", a year long series of lectures, exhibitions and events. Although the Center houses several entities, the vast majority of the information in the collection pertains to Archives & Special Collections.
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center
History
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, a division of the University of Connecticut Libraries, was created by the merger of Special Collections and Historical Manuscripts and Archives in 1995. The new area moved into the Dodd Research Center upon its opening. President William Clinton officiated at the dedication of the Center and kicked off the "Dodd Year", a year-long series of lectures, exhibitions and events.
Scope and Content
The collection contains correspondence, publications, fliers, brochures, plans, drawings, photographs and ephemeral materials pertaining to the operation of the Dodd Research Center and its programs. Over time additional files pertaining to the operation of Special Collections and Historical Manuscripts and Archives have been added, creating some overlap between Series II-V. All materials relate to the functioning of the Archives & Special Collections area as a unit of the University of Connecticut Libraries.
Arrangement
Series I: Dodd Year ( undated, 1988-1996 )
Series II: Administrative Records ( undated, 1988- )
Series III: Program Records ( undated, 1992- )
Series IV: Publications ( undated, 1976- )
Series V: Predecessor Departments ( undated, 1965-1997 )
Series VI: Media ( undated, ) includes Cornell West and other recorded lectures as well as photographs of A& SC events.
Separated Material
The following materials have been separated from the collection and cataloged:
Connecticut History Online Reception Dodd Video 108
Connecticut Children's Book fair Lecture, November 9, 2001 Dodd Video 111
Teale Lecture Series by Joseph Bruchac Dodd Video 388
UConn Sackler Lecture on Human Rights with Harold Koh October 2, 2007 Dodd DVD 93
Readings from Sen. Chris Dodd's Book "Letters from Nuremburg" October 1, 2007 Dodd DVD 94
2004 Strochlitz Presentation Dr. Philip Nel, Writing Lives Ruth Krauss and Crockett Johnson [damaged, removed 2/8/2010]
Birthing a New Healthcare System, Nancy Johnson, March 24, 2008 Dodd Video 397
Edwin Way Teale Lecture Series, Gary Snyder 1998-0290.ac1
Rabbi Poupico, Konover Dedication 1998-0290.ac2
Teale Lecture Series 2006-2007, David Allen Sibley, April 12, 2007; 1998-0290.vr1
50 Years Later 1998-0290.vr2
3rd Annual CT Teacher's Conference, October 22, 1999; 1998-0290.vr3
Grant Writing Seminar 1998-0290.vr4
Death Penalty in CT "Hot Issues" Forum September 26, 2001; 1998-0290.vr5
Doris and Simon Konover Speaker, Rabbi Kesler, President Hartley 1998-0290.ac3
RBS Greenwich Capital Economic Seminar: Peter Fisher 1998-0290.dvd1
Acquisition Information
The materials in the collection have been periodically transferred by the area staff to the University Archives.
Related Material
Archives & Special Collections has a substantial collection of materials pertaining to the University, its history, administration, faculty, staff and students, etc.]. For detailed information on these collections please contact the curator or ask at the Reading Room desk.
Access
The collection is open and available for research.
University of Connecticut.; Administrative Records.; Audio cassettes.; Audio visual materials.; Blueprints.; Correspondence.; Financial Records.; Fliers. [printed matter]; Minutes.; Notes.; Photocopies.; Photographs.; Press releases.; Publications.; Sound recordings.; Storrs (Conn.); Videocassettes.
- Series I: Dodd Year, undated, 1988-1996
  - Breaking Ground for History, 1993 (Box 1:1)
  - Centers for Judaic Studies and Oral History - Dedication, 1996 (Box 1:2)
  - Clippings (of the Dodd Year), 1995-1996 (Box 1:3)
  - Concert--Dedication, 1995 October 15 (Box 22:, Folder 704)
  - Fine Arts Catalogue, 1995 (Box 1:4)
  - Fundraising brochure, undated (Box 1:5)
  - Konover Auditorium - Dedication, 1996 (Box 1:6)
  - Opening Events Program, 1995 (Box 1:7)
  - Programs, 1995 (Box 1:8)
    - Sunday, 1995 (Box 1:9)
    - Monday, 1995 (Box 1:10)
    - Tuesday, 1995 (Box 1:11)
    - Wednesday, 1995 (Box 1:12)
  - Publicity - Dedication, 1995 (Box 1:13)
  - Remembrance Day, Soliloquy for a Passing Century for Wind Ensemble by Morton Gould, inscribed by composer, 1995 (Box 8:411)
  - Speakers
    - Arias, Oscar, 1995 (Box 1:14-15)
    - Clinton, William J., 1995 (Box 1:16-17)
    - Gray, William, 1995 (Box 1:18)
    - King, Henry T., Jr., 1995 (Box 1:19)
    - Wiesel, Elie, 1988, 1995 (Box 1:20-21)
  - Tickets - Dedication, 1995 (Box 1:22)
  - Fifty Years After Nuremberg: Human Rights and the Rule of Law, 1995-1996
    - Apron, undated (Box 1:23)
    - Buttons, undated, 1996 (Box 1:24)
    - Closing Events, 1996 (Box 1:25)
    - Flyers, ca. 1995-1996 (Box 1:26)
    - Media's View of the Opening Events of UConn's Commemoration..., 1995 (Box 1:27)
    - Opening Events, 1995 (Box 1:28)
    - Publications, posters, flyers, 1995-1996 (Box 8:412)
    - Witnesses to Nuremberg, ca. 1995 (Box 1:29)
- Series II: Administrative Records, undated, 1988-
  - Accession - Collection Development, undated, 1968-2005 (Box 32)
  - 125th Anniversary Book, 2002 (Box 13:564)
  - Annual Report Printing Quotes, 2002 (Box 13:565)
  - Annual Report Files, 2002 (Box 13:566)
  - Annual Report Working files, 2002-2003 (Box 13:567)
  - Annual Report (1995-2005) (Box 19:, Folder 599)
  - Annual Report, 2006 (Box 22)
  - Banner, undated (Box 28)
  - Brochures
    - African-American Vernacular Music, 2001 (Box 13:572)
    - Alternative Press Collection, undated, ca. 2000 (Box 1:30)
    - Archives and Special Collections, 1995, 2000 (Box 1:31)
    - Business and Labor, 1999 (Box 13:570)
    - Center for Judaic Studies, undated, ca. 2002 (Box 1:32)
    - Center for Oral History, undated (Box 1:33)
    - Connecticut History Online, circa 1999 (Box 21:, Folder 626)
    - Digital Collection Forum, 2001, 2002 (Box 1:34)
    - Dodd Center, 2000 (Box 1:35)
    - Dodd Center, 2000 (Box 13:569)
    - Exhibitions (Library brochures), undated (Box 21:, Folder 646)
    - Hispanic History, 1997, ca. 2000 (Box 1:36)
    - Historical Manuscripts and Archives, undated (Box 1:37)
    - Holocaust Curriculum Guide, 1999 (Box 1:38)
    - Latin American and Hispanic Studies, 1990 (Box 1:39)
    - Law, War and Human Rights, 1995 (Box 1:40)
    - Literary Resources and Research Opportunities, undated (Box 1:41)
    - Northeast Children's Literature Collection, undated, 1999 (Box 1:42)
    - Northeast Children's Literature Collection Endowment, 2005 (Box 21:, Folder 624)
    - Nursing Leadership, undated (Box 1:43)
    - Political Collections, 2006 (Box 21:, Folder 673)
    - Railroad History, 1999-2000 (Box 13:568)
    - Special Collections, undated (Box 1:44)
    - Survey Research, 2002 (Box 13:571)
    - Thomas J. Dodd Papers, 1995 (Box 1:45)
    - University Archives, 2006 (Box 21:, Folder 674)
    - Archives and Research at the University of Connecticut, undated (Box 22)
  - Dodd Prize and Sackler Lecture Invitations, October 2007 (Box 22)
  - ABC Newsletter, 2007-2008 (Box 22)
  - Dodd Program for Study of Human Rights and International Justice, undated (Box 22)
  - Dodd Prize/Letters from Nuremberg Program, October 1, 2007 (Box 22)
  - UConn Traditions "Reflections on Human Rights", 1996 (Box 22)
  - Sackler Lecture Invitations and Program, 2006-2008 (Box 22)
  - General Correspondence, 1988-2008 (Box 22)
  - Donor Correspondence, 1989-1996 (Box 22)
  - UConn Traditions "Reflections on Human Rights", 1996 (Box 22)
  - Building Design and specification records, undated (Box 15)
  - Building Files (D. Kapp), undated (Box 14, 20)
  - Collection Management - LSCA, undated, 1983-2005 (Box 33)
  - Collection survey, circa 1998 (Box 16)
  - Construction
    - Equipment List, undated (Box 7:419)
  - Director's Files, undated, 1995-2008 (Box 29-31)
  - Encoded Archival Description (EAD) conversion (LWPO), 2005 (Box 23)
  - Ephemera (Jail items), 1996 (Box 8, 16)
  - FAQ, 1997 (Box 16:576)
  - Floor plans, undated (Box 16)
  - Fundraising information, undated (Box 16:578)
  - Grants
    - Connecticut History Online I (IMLS)
      - Director's files, 1998- (Box 24)
      - Proposal, 1998 (Box 1:46-47)
      - Publicity, undated (Box 1:48)
    - Connecticut History Online II (IMLS)
      - Proposal, 1999 (Box 1:49)
    - Electronic Records
      - Academic Information Technology Planning Committee Final Report, 1998 (Box 1:50)
      - Advisory Board, 1999 (Box 1:51)
      - Consultant Report, 1999 (Box 2:52)
      - Correspondence, 2000 (Box 2:53)
      - DOIT Survey, 2000 (Box 2:54)
      - Electronic Records Management
        - Australia, 2000 (Box 2:55)
        - Cornell University (Box 2:56)
        - University of Idaho, 1999 (Box 2:57)
        - Indiana University, 1999 (Box 2:58)
        - Kansas State Historical Society, 1999 (Box 2:59)
        - National Archives and Records Administration, 2000 (Box 2:60)
        - Oregon State University, 1999 (Box 2:61)
      - Financial Reports, 1998-2000 (Box 2:62)
      - Grant Proposal, 1999-2000 (Box 2:63)
      - Interim Report, 2000 (Box 2:64)
      - Minutes, 2000 April (Box 2:65)
      - Minutes, 2000 May (Box 2:66)
      - Outline, handouts, etc., 2000 June (Box 2:67)
      - New York State documents, 1999-2000 (Box 2:68)
      - PeopleSoft, June 2000 (Box 2:69)
      - Personal Service Agreement [Restricted], 2000 (Box 2:70)
      - Presentation-Advisory Board, 2000 September (Box 2:71)
      - Notes and Minutes (Draft-BP), 2000 (Box 2:72)
      - Documents for Chancellor's Staff Meeting, 2000 (Box 2:73)
      - Draft 1 - Strategic Plan, 2000 August (Box 2:74)
      - Draft 2 - Strategic Plan, 2000 September (Box 2:75)
      - Draft 5 - Strategic Plan, 2000 October (Box 2:76)
      - Draft 8 - Strategic Plan, 2000 November (Box 2:77)
      - Tom's Files, 1999-2002 (Box 13:562-563)
      - Working Documents, 1999-2000 (Box 2:78)
    - NHPRC Fellow, 1997-1998
      General note
      [Folders contain articles, notes and materials authored by or relevant to folder heading.]
      - Abraham, Terry (Box 2:82)
      - Barry, Rick (Box 2:79)
      - Bearman, David (Box 2:80)
      - Bibliography (Box 2:81)
      - Cook, Terry (Box 2:83)
      - Council of State Historical Records Coordinators (Box 2:84)
      - Delaware Project (Box 2:85)
      - Digital Collections: A strategy policy framework... (Box 2:86)
      - Florida (Box 2:87)
      - Grant proposals-examples (Box 2:88)
      - Hollinger, Richard (Box 2:89)
      - Indiana University (Box 2:90)
      - Institute of Museum and Information Services (Box 2:91)
      - InterPARES (Box 2:92)
      - Malaysia Seminars (Box 2:93)
      - Management of electronic records: Issues and Guidelines (Box 2:94)
      - Massachusetts (Box 2:95)
      - McGovern and Samuels (Box 2:96)
      - Models (Box 2:97)
      - National Historical Publications and Records Commission (Box 2:98)
      - National Endowment for the Humanities (Box 2:99)
      - New England Council of Presidents (NECOP) (Box 2:100)
      - New South Wales (Box 2:101)
      - Personnel Sources for Electronic Records (Box 2:102)
      - University of Pittsburgh (Box 2:103)
      - Research Libraries Group (RLG) (Box 2:104)
      - Rhode Island Historical Records Advisory Board (Box 2:105)
      - Strategic Plans
        - University of Arizona (Box 2:106)
        - University of Maryland (Box 2:107)
        - State of Connecticut (Box 2:108)
        - Mission statements/visions (Box 2:109)
        - University of Tennessee (Box 2:110)
      - University of British Columbia (Box 2:111)
      - Vermont (Box 2:112)
    - New Haven Railroad Processing (NEH), ca. 1986-1990
      - AMC worksheets (Box 2:113)
      - Appraisal (Box 2:114)
      - Hagley Museum Penn Central Archives (Box 2:115)
      - Hagley Museum Final Report (Box 2:116)
      - Bound Volumes shelf tags (Box 2:117)
      - Bound Volumes "Missing" (Box 2:118)
      - Bridgeport Library correspondence (Box 2:119)
      - Brochure (Box 2:120)
      - Budget and Finances (NEH) (Box 2:121)
      - Claims sampling (Box 2:122)
      - Connecticut Trolley Museum (Box 2:123)
      - Conrail Valuation records - instruction (Box 2:124)
      - Potential donors (Box 2:125)
      - Duplicate sales (Box 3:126)
      - Friends of the Railroad (draft) (Box 3:127)
      - Flyer (Box 3:128)
      - Fundraising/UConn Foundation (Box 3:129)
      - Grant application - NEH (Box 3:130)
      - Grant correspondence (Box 3:131)
      - Grant letters of support (Box 3:132)
      - Historical background (Box 3:133)
      - Levitt, Alan (Box 3:134)
      - Logo (Box 3:135)
      - Mailing lists (Box 3:136)
      - Metro North correspondence (Box 3:137)
      - NEH reports (Box 3:138)
      - Pre-Grant inventories (Box 3:139)
      - Publicity (Box 3:140-141)
      - Reference (Box 3:142)
      - Connecticut Railroad facts and trivia (Box 3:143)
      - Syracuse (Register) (Box 3:144)
      - Harvard (Register) (Box 3:145)
      - Virginia (Register) (Box 3:146)
      - Records to Yale (Box 3:147)
      - Valuation maps (Box 3:148)
      - Valuation maps subdivision (Box 3:149)
      - Maps inventory (Box 3:150)
      - Fumigation (Box 3:151)
      - Photographs Collection (Box 3:152)
      - NEH Grant proposal (Box 3:153)
      - NHRHTA Correspondence (Box 3:154)
    - Records Management/Records Survey (NHPRC), 1982-1990
      - Records survey publicity (Box 3:155)
      - General information (Box 3:156)
      - Filing and recordkeeping manual (Box 3:157)
      - Correspondence (Box 3:158)
      - Records transfer (Box 3:159)
      - Records Center (Box 3:160)
      - Records retention for personnel (Box 3:161)
      - Letter accompanying requests (Box 3:162)
      - Disposal forms (Box 3:163)
      - Records transfer forms (Box 3:164)
      - Records transfers (Box 3:165)
      - Records Mangement 1993 (Box 3:166)
      - Records Management 1991-1992 (Box 3:167)
      - Records Management 1991 (Box 3:168)
      - Records Management 1990 (Box 3:169)
      - Records Management 1989 (Box 3:170)
      - Records Management 1988 (Box 3:171)
      - Records Management 1987 (Box 3:172)
      - Records Management transfer of responsibility (Box 3:173)
      - Public records general letters (Box 3:174)
      - Articles (Box 3:175)
      - Correspondence (Box 3:176)
      - Staff meeting minutes (Box 3:177)
        - 1996 (Box 16:, Folder 586)
      - Records Survey report (Box 3:178)
      - NHPRC report (Box 3:179-182)
      - NHPRC correspondence (Box 3:183)
      - Filing manual (Box 3:184)
      - Grant proposal (Box 3:185)
      - Forms (Box 3:186)
      - Records Center (Box 3:187)
      - Archives Grant proposal (Box 3:188)
      - Grant proposal notes and background (Box 4:189)
      - Authorization letter (Box 4:190)
      - UConn records management (Box 4:191)
      - Connecticut Statutes (Box 4:192)
      - NHPRC Grant - Travel and Supplies (Box 4:193)
      - Time and effort reports (Box 4:194)
      - Correspondence (Box 4:195)
      - Letters of appreciation (Box 4:196)
      - Materials received due to records survey (Box 4:197)
      - Personnel retention policy (Box 4:198)
      - Thank you notes (Box 4:199)
      - Telephone survey forms for historical material (Box 4:200)
      - Potential archival material (Box 4:201)
      - Records retention research project (Box 4:202)
      - Retention schedule problems (Box 4:203)
      - Visits - Units completed (Box 4:204)
      - Offices called - not surveyed (Box 4:205)
      - Financial offices (Box 4:206)
      - Health Center correspondence (Box 4:207)
      - Health Center (Box 4:208)
      - Law School correspondence (Box 4:209)
      - Records survey - Slide/tape program script (Box 4:210)
      - UConn buildings (Box 4:211)
      - Stamford Regional campus (Box 4:212)
      - VP for Finance and Administration report (Box 4:213)
      - Law School report (Box 4:214)
      - Survey report - Responses (Box 4:215)
      - Publicity (Box 4:216)
      - Yale University Archives Survey report (Box 4:217)
      - Health Center report (Box 4:218)
      - Records Survey (Box 4:219)
      - Records Survey - Correspondence and Notes (Box 4:220)
    - Charles Olson-Herman Melville (Delmas)
    - UConn-ANC Processing (Mellon)
    - New England Archivists Education Project (NHPRC, NEH), 1987-1990
      [See also: New England Archivists Records.]
      - NEH application masters (2nd proposal) (Box 4:221)
      - Letters of support (Box 4:222)
      - NHPRC Correspondence (Box 4:223)
      - Grant proposal (Box 4:224)
      - Budget (Box 4:225)
      - NHPRC Grant application master (2nd proposal) (Box 4:226)
      - Project proposal (Box 4:227)
      - NHPRC Grant guidelines (Box 4:228)
      - Project personnel (Box 4:229)
      - Correspondence (Box 4:230)
      - Julie Bressor (Box 4:231)
    - Connecticut Labor Records Project (NEH, AFL-CIO, Labor Education Center), 1980-
      - Connecticut Labor Records survey proposal (Box 4:232)
      - NEH Labor records poject (not funded) (Box 4:233)
      - Preliminary proposals (Box 4:234)
      - NEH correspondence (Box 4:235)
      - AFL-CIO processing grant (Box 4:236)
      - NEH reports (Box 4:237)
      - Labor Education Center (Box 4:238)
      - Publicity (Box 4:239)
      - Brochure (Box 4:240)
      - Conference on Records of American Labor - report (Box 4:241)
      - Documenting Labor in America Conference (George Meany Center, 1985 April 1-2) (Box 4:242)
      - Deposit agreement forms (Box 4:243)
      - Survey forms (Box 4:244)
      - Reference file (Box 4:245)
      - Vertical file (Box 4:246)
      - Labor groups correspondence (Box 4:247)
      - AFL-CIO (Box 4:248)
      - AFL-CIO Statement on Labor Archives (Box 4:249)
      - AFL-CIO histories and publications (Box 4:250)
  - Management Council - Weather Emergencies, undated, 1978-2008 (Box 34)
  - Opportunities for Support, undated (Box 16:577)
  - Report - Systems Recommendation, 1998 (Box 5:251)
  - Shelf Read forms, 1998 (Box 21:, Folder 681)
  - Tour Script, 1997 (Box 5:252)
  - University Archivist's files, 1997-2005 (Box 25-26)
  - User Survey, 2000 April (Box 5:253)
  - Visioning, 2000 (Box 5:254)
  - Accession record, superceded, 1967-1979 (Box 22)
  - Dodd Center acquisitions, undated (Box 22)
  - Notes of meetings with University Administration and faculty, 1979-1980 (Box 22)
  - Miscellaneous, including staffing prior, 1987-1994 (Box 22)
  - Polish-Jewish Archives, 1993 (Box 22)
  - Committee on Archival Policy, 1971-1979 (Box 22)
  - Maps and Drawings: Proposal on Processing and Description, undated (Box 22)
  - Publicity, 1980-1994 (Box 22)
  - Center for Excellence, 1987 (Box 22)
  - Wilbur Cross renovations, use of space, 1992-1993 (Box 22)
  - DRC Talk Transcript, undated (Box 25)
  - History of the Library Transcript, undated (Box 25)
  - Dodd Staff Meetings, 1996-1998 (Box 24)
- Series III: Program Records, undated, 1992-
  - Book fair, undated
    - Authors Brochures (Box 5:255)
    - Clippings (Box 5:256)
  - Book fair, 1992
    - Announcements (Box 5:257)
    - Funding (Box 5:258)
    - Planning (Box 5:259)
    - Publicity (Box 5:260)
    - Publicity (Box 8:413)
    - Roger's File (Box 27:, Folder 696)
    - Verne's File (Box 16)
    - Volunteers (Box 5:261)
  - Book fair, 1993
    - "Choice Fare" (Box 5:262)
    - Clippings (Box 5:263)
    - Correspondence (Box 5:264)
    - Ellen's File (Box 5:265)
    - Funding (Box 5:266)
    - Publicity (Box 5:267)
    - Publicity (Box 8:414)
    - Roger's File (Box 27:, Folder 696)
    - Volunteers (Box 5:268)
  - Book fair, 1994
    - Addresses (Box 5:269)
    - Agenda/Minutes (Box 5:270)
    - Authors/Illustrators (Box 5:271)
    - Correspondence (Box 5:272)
    - Ellen's File (Box 5:273)
    - Finances (Box 5:274)
    - Funding (Box 5:275)
    - Planning (Box 5:276)
    - Poster (Box 8:415)
    - Publicity (Box 5:277)
    - Roger's File (Box 27:, Folder 697)
    - Storytelling (Box 5:278)
  - Book fair, 1995
    - Addresses (Box 5:279)
    - Authors/Illustrators (Box 5:280)
    - Brochures (Box 5:281)
    - Budget (Box 5:282)
    - Cash Expenses-receipts (Box 5:283)
    - Committee (Box 5:284)
    - Correspondence (Box 5:285)
    - Ellen's File (Box 5:286)
    - Flyer requests (Box 5:287)
    - Funding (Box 5:288)
    - Letterhead (Box 5:289)
    - Minutes (Box 5:290)
    - Publicity (Box 5:291)
    - Receipts (Box 5:292)
    - Roger's File (Box 27:, Folder 698-701)
    - Survey (Box 5:293)
    - Volunteers (Box 5:294)
  - Book fair, 1996
    - Addresses (Box 5:295)
    - Agenda/Minutes (Box 5:296)
    - Announcements/Flyers (Box 5:297)
    - Auerbach Schiro Koopman House Brochure (Box 5:298)
    - Authors/Illustrators (Box 5:299)
    - Banner (Box 5:300)
    - Bishop Center (Box 5:301)
    - Books itemized by author/illustrators (Box 5:302)
    - Clippings (Box 5:303)
    - Committee (Box 5:304)
    - Correspondence (Box 5:305)
    - Dinner (Box 5:306)
    - Food and hospitality (Box 5:307)
    - Funding (Box 5:308)
    - Information Desk (Box 5:309)
    - Logo (Box 5:310)
    - Organizational Files (Box 5:311)
    - Presentations (Box 5:312)
    - Previous Years' Information (Box 5:313)
    - Program (Box 5:314)
    - Publicity (Box 5:315)
    - Roger's File (Box 27:, Folder 702)
    - Schools/Flyers (Box 5:316)
    - Storytelling (Box 5:317)
    - Summary (Box 5:318)
    - Survey (Box 5:319)
    - Volunteers (Box 5:320)
    - Zip Code Breakdown (Box 5:321)
  - Book fair, 1997
    - Addresses (Box 5:322)
    - Agenda/Minutes (Box 5:323)
    - Clippings (Box 5:324)
    - Correspondence (Box 5:325)
    - Dinner (Box 5:326)
    - Ellen's File (Box 5:327)
    - Favors (Dinner) (Box 6:328)
    - Finances (Box 6:329)
    - Flyers (Box 6:330)
    - Funding (Box 6:331)
    - Planning (Box 6:332)
    - Program (Box 6:333)
    - Publicity (Box 6:334)
    - Summary (Box 6:335)
    - Teacher's Conference Program (Box 6:336)
    - Terri's File (Box 6:337)
    - Volunteers (Box 6:338)
  - Book fair, 1998
    - Agenda/Minutes (Box 6:339)
    - Author/Illustrator Brochures (Box 6:340)
    - Clippings (Box 6:341)
    - Correspondence (Box 6:342)
    - Dinner (Box 6:343)
    - Finances (Box 6:344)
    - Funding (Box 6:345)
    - Planning (Box 6:346)
    - Program (Box 6:347)
    - Publicity (Box 6:348)
    - Teachers' Conference (Jean's File) (Box 6:349)
    - Terri's File (Box 6:350)
    - Volunteers (Box 6:351)
  - Book fair, 1999
    - Addresses (Box 6:352)
    - Correspondence (Box 6:353)
    - Dinner (Box 6:354)
    - Finances (Box 6:355)
    - Planning (Box 6:356)
    - Program/Flyer (Box 6:357)
    - Program, 1999 (Box 21:, Folder 629)
    - Publicity (Box 6:358)
    - Raab Associates prize (Box 16:, Folder 695)
    - Teacher's Conference (Box 16:573)
    - Volunteers (Box 6:359)
  - Book fair, 2000
    - Bookmark (Box 21:, Folder 630)
    - Favors (Dinner) (Box 6:360)
    - Invitation (Dinner) (Box 6:361)
    - Program (Box 6:362)
    - Program (Box 21:, Folder 631)
    - Raab Associates prize (Box 16:, Folder 593)